hottestfashiononline.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Hottest Fashion Online

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

### **What information do we collect?**

  * At **HottestFashionOnline.Com** we collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
  * When  registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit  **HottestFashionOnline.Com** anonymously.
  * For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the [ DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) on  **HottestFashionOnline.Com**   displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

**HottestFashionOnline.Com**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### **Online Privacy Policy**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### **Terms and Conditions**

**Disclaimer:** Some of Contents(Videos, photos) on  **HottestFashionOnline.Com** are publicly available on the internet and property of their respective owners.  **HottestFashionOnline.Com** is not responsible in case of any illegal and unappropriated usage of contents by visitors.

Copyrights: All Articles and text based information on **HottestFashionOnline.Com** is originally developed by **HottestFashionOnline.Com** team, distribution and copying such information without linking back to original source is against terms and conditions of ****HottestFashionOnline.Com****
